<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tags on Fujimoto Writes</title><link>https://fujimotowrites.com/tags/</link><description>Recent content in Tags on Fujimoto Writes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fujimotowrites.com/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Holidays 2024</title><link>https://fujimotowrites.com/posts/holidays-2024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://fujimotowrites.com/posts/holidays-2024/</guid><description>&lt;p>Happy holidays!We hope everyone had a wonderful 2024.&lt;/p>&lt;p>The biggest event for us this year (by far) was getting married inAugust, at McMenamins Anderson School not far from where we live inBothell, WA.The ceremony and reception were everything we could have dreamed of andmore.Seeing both our families together was a treat we will cherish forever.&lt;/p>&lt;p>A few days after the excitement of the wedding, we took our honeymoon atPoipu on Kauai island, Hawaii.It was blissful to relax in pools and have divine dining experiences.&lt;/p>&lt;p>&lt;img src="dance1.jpeg#float" alt="Dancing the Cha Cha">Our passion for ballroom dance grew over the course of the year,crescendoing in October when we participated in our first competition:Summit DanceSport about 20 miles south of us.We even won several first places, albeit when competing uncontested.It was an honor to compete alongside our teacher and another couple fromour studio.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Tynor moved on from Amazon after almost two and a half years.He now works at Peach Finance, a finance tech company that works withlenders to provide loan services.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Mallory is still working at Pfizer as a senior associate scientist.She enjoys crafting, playing guitar, and seeing live shows including abenefit concert by Patty Griffin at Benaroya Hall in Seattle.&lt;/p>&lt;p>In March, we took a trip up to Vancouver, BC and saw Dancing with theStars live, featuring pro dancers from the show.Our visiting around Vancouver was impeded by cold weather and rain, butwe still found some good food, enjoyed the show, and the weather clearedup enough for us to walk around Stanley Park before we headed home.&lt;/p>&lt;p>We are looking forward to more adventures in 2025, and wish everyone arelaxing holidays and happy new year!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>